moneyupload.com 2010-05-11

# Register for getting Free Download File Hosting Free Upload Free File Sharing, Register to be rich

When you register with us, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name and email address. 

We take reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our members and ensure that the personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without the member’s consent. MoneyUpload.com has numerous security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of our members’ information. All member information is password protected and only accessible by authorized staff of MoneyUpload.com. 

However, there may be times when MoneyUpload.com may be required to disclose personal information of a member without his/her express consent when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the member.

While MoneyUpload.com, our associates and affiliates make every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people that neither we nor you will know. 

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to our Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to be bound by our terms, we politely ask that you do not use this site.
